<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string-array name="movie_genres">
        <item>@string/action</item>
        <item>@string/animation</item>
        <item>@string/adventure</item>
        <item>@string/comedy</item>
        <item>@string/documentary</item>
        <item>@string/sci_fi</item>
        <item>@string/thriller</item>
        <item>@string/horror</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="popular_movies_names">
        <item>"Spider-Man - No Way Home"</item>
        <item>"Encanto"</item>
        <item>"The King's Man"</item>
        <item>"X-Men Origins: Wolverine"</item>
        <item>"The Amazing Spider-Man"</item>
        <item>"The Incredible Hulk"</item>
        <item>"Taxi Driver"</item>
        <item>"Scarface"</item>
        <item>"Pulp Fiction"</item>
        <item>"Fight Club"</item>
    </string-array>

    <integer-array name="popular_movies_images">
        <item>@drawable/movie_spider_man_no_way_home</item>
        <item>@drawable/movie_encanto</item>
        <item>@drawable/movie_the_kings_man</item>
        <item>@drawable/movie_x_men_origins_wolverine</item>
        <item>@drawable/movie_the_amazing_spider_man</item>
        <item>@drawable/movie_the_incredible_hulk</item>
        <item>@drawable/movie_taxi_driver</item>
        <item>@drawable/movie_scarface</item>
        <item>@drawable/movie_pulp_fiction</item>
        <item>@drawable/movie_fight_club</item>
    </integer-array>

    <integer-array name="popular_movies_year">
        <item>2021</item>
        <item>2021</item>
        <item>2021</item>
        <item>2009</item>
        <item>2012</item>
        <item>2008</item>
        <item>1976</item>
        <item>1983</item>
        <item>1994</item>
        <item>1999</item>
    </integer-array>

    <string-array name="popular_movies_descriptions">
        <item>"Peter Parker is unmasked and no longer able to separate his normal life from the high-stakes of being a super-hero. When he asks for help from Doctor Strange the stakes become even more dangerous, forcing him to discover what it truly means to be Spider-Man."</item>
        <item>"The tale of an extraordinary family, the Madrigals, who live hidden in the mountains of Colombia, in a magical house, in a vibrant town, in a wondrous, charmed place called an Encanto. The magic of the Encanto has blessed every child in the family with a unique gift from super strength to the power to heal—every child except one, Mirabel. But when she discovers that the magic surrounding the Encanto is in danger, Mirabel decides that she, the only ordinary Madrigal, might just be her exceptional family's last hope."</item>
        <item>"As a collection of history's worst tyrants and criminal masterminds gather to plot a war to wipe out millions, one man must race against time to stop them."</item>
        <item>"After seeking to live a normal life, Logan sets out to avenge the death of his girlfriend by undergoing the mutant Weapon X program and becoming Wolverine."</item>
        <item>"Peter Parker is an outcast high schooler abandoned by his parents as a boy, leaving him to be raised by his Uncle Ben and Aunt May. Like most teenagers, Peter is trying to figure out who he is and how he got to be the person he is today. As Peter discovers a mysterious briefcase that belonged to his father, he begins a quest to understand his parents' disappearance – leading him directly to Oscorp and the lab of Dr. Curt Connors, his father's former partner. As Spider-Man is set on a collision course with Connors' alter ego, The Lizard, Peter will make life-altering choices to use his powers and shape his destiny to become a hero."</item>
        <item>"Scientist Bruce Banner scours the planet for an antidote to the unbridled force of rage within him: the Hulk. But when the military masterminds who dream of exploiting his powers force him back to civilization, he finds himself coming face to face with a new, deadly foe."</item>
        <item>"A mentally unstable Vietnam War veteran works as a night-time taxi driver in New York City where the perceived decadence and sleaze feed his urge for violent action, attempting to save a preadolescent prostitute in the process."</item>
        <item>"After getting a green card in exchange for assassinating a Cuban government official, Tony Montana stakes a claim on the drug trade in Miami. Viciously murdering anyone who stands in his way, Tony eventually becomes the biggest drug lord in the state, controlling nearly all the cocaine that comes through Miami. But increased pressure from the police, wars with Colombian drug cartels and his own drug-fueled paranoia serve to fuel the flames of his eventual downfall."</item>
        <item>"A burger-loving hit man, his philosophical partner, a drug-addled gangster's moll and a washed-up boxer converge in this sprawling, comedic crime caper. Their adventures unfurl in three stories that ingeniously trip back and forth in time."</item>
        <item>"Wtf, dude? Do you even remember the first rule?"</item>
    </string-array>

    <integer-array name="popular_movies_duration">
        <item>136</item>
        <item>89</item>
        <item>127</item>
        <item>107</item>
        <item>136</item>
        <item>112</item>
        <item>114</item>
        <item>170</item>
        <item>154</item>
        <item>139</item>
    </integer-array>

    <string-array name="popular_movies_genres">
        <item>@string/adventure</item>
        <item>@string/animation</item>
        <item>@string/action</item>
        <item>@string/sci_fi</item>
        <item>@string/adventure</item>
        <item>@string/sci_fi</item>
        <item>@string/drama</item>
        <item>@string/action</item>
        <item>@string/thriller</item>
        <item>@string/drama</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>